<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Deployment Options on</title><link>https://docs.builder-toolkit.partner.aws.dev/docs-abp-project-type/deployment-options/index.html</link><description>Recent content in Deployment Options on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>&amp;copy; {{YEAR}}, Amazon Web Services, Inc. or its affiliates. All rights reserved.</copyright><atom:link href="https://docs.builder-toolkit.partner.aws.dev/docs-abp-project-type/deployment-options/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Launch ABI using CloudFormation Templates</title><link>https://docs.builder-toolkit.partner.aws.dev/docs-abp-project-type/deployment-options/launch-using-cloudformation/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.builder-toolkit.partner.aws.dev/docs-abp-project-type/deployment-options/launch-using-cloudformation/index.html</guid><description>Launch the cloudformation template provided as part /templates/ in the Management Account of the organization.
Download the cloudformation template from source: https://aws-abi-pilot.s3.us-east-1.amazonaws.com/cfn-abi-aws-reference-guide/templates/abi-enable-partner1-securityhub-integration.yaml
Launch CloudFormation template in your AWS Control Tower home region.
Stack name: launch-abi-sample-partner-integration ARN of partner integration to turn on in AWS Security Hub: arn:aws:securityhub:$[taskcat_current_region]::product/cloud-custodian/cloud-custodian Leave the remaining values default. Choose both the Capabilities and select Submit to launch the stack.
[] I acknowledge that AWS CloudFormation might create IAM resources with custom names.</description></item><item><title>Launch ABI using Customizations for Control Tower (CfCT)</title><link>https://docs.builder-toolkit.partner.aws.dev/docs-abp-project-type/deployment-options/launch-using-cfct/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.builder-toolkit.partner.aws.dev/docs-abp-project-type/deployment-options/launch-using-cfct/index.html</guid><description>Customizations for AWS Control Tower combines AWS Control Tower and other highly-available, trusted AWS services to help customers more quickly set up a secure, multi-account AWS environment using AWS best practices. You can easily add customizations to your AWS Control Tower landing zone using an AWS CloudFormation template and service control policies (SCPs). You can deploy the custom template and policies to individual accounts and organizational units (OUs) within your organization.</description></item></channel></rss>