<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Docs on</title><link>https://docs.builder-toolkit.partner.aws.dev/docs-abp-project-type/docs/</link><description>Recent content in Docs on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>&amp;copy; {{YEAR}}, Amazon Web Services, Inc. or its affiliates. All rights reserved.</copyright><atom:link href="https://docs.builder-toolkit.partner.aws.dev/docs-abp-project-type/docs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title/><link>https://docs.builder-toolkit.partner.aws.dev/docs-abp-project-type/docs/available_modules/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.builder-toolkit.partner.aws.dev/docs-abp-project-type/docs/available_modules/</guid><description>List of available ABI modules AWS Service Name Repository AWS Security Hub cfn-abi-aws-securityhub AWS GuardDuty cfn-abi-amazon-guardduty AWS Control Tower cfn-abi-aws-cloudtrail</description></item><item><title/><link>https://docs.builder-toolkit.partner.aws.dev/docs-abp-project-type/docs/cleanup-instructions/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.builder-toolkit.partner.aws.dev/docs-abp-project-type/docs/cleanup-instructions/</guid><description>Cleanup Instructions</description></item><item><title/><link>https://docs.builder-toolkit.partner.aws.dev/docs-abp-project-type/docs/cost-considerations/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.builder-toolkit.partner.aws.dev/docs-abp-project-type/docs/cost-considerations/</guid><description>Cost considertions</description></item><item><title/><link>https://docs.builder-toolkit.partner.aws.dev/docs-abp-project-type/docs/faqs/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.builder-toolkit.partner.aws.dev/docs-abp-project-type/docs/faqs/</guid><description>FAQs Q: How to add internal AWS contributors? A: Access to the repositories are controlled from the builder platform interface. Refer to ABP usage guide for steps.
Q: How to add contributors from partner side? A: Use the same mechanism mentioned above to manage access to the repository. If you are a partner trying to access these repos, reach out your assigned AWS PSA.
Q: How do I add secrets to the parameters in the taskcat file?</description></item><item><title/><link>https://docs.builder-toolkit.partner.aws.dev/docs-abp-project-type/docs/how-to-build-abi-project/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.builder-toolkit.partner.aws.dev/docs-abp-project-type/docs/how-to-build-abi-project/</guid><description>How to build an ABI project Once you have access to the reposity, fork the repository. Additional information available in Fork a repo article.
Refer to below examples to create a fork from CLI.
gh auth login gh repo fork https://github.com/aws-ia/cfn-abi-aws-reference-guide.git Add the required ABI Modules as submodules to your repository (example below to add securityhub repo).
mkdir submodules cd submodules git submodule add https://github.com/aws-ia/cfn-abi-aws-securityhub.git List of all available ABI Modules are Available here.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://docs.builder-toolkit.partner.aws.dev/docs-abp-project-type/docs/launch-using-cfct/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.builder-toolkit.partner.aws.dev/docs-abp-project-type/docs/launch-using-cfct/</guid><description>Launch ABI using Customizations for Control Tower (CfCT) Customizations for AWS Control Tower combines AWS Control Tower and other highly-available, trusted AWS services to help customers more quickly set up a secure, multi-account AWS environment using AWS best practices. You can easily add customizations to your AWS Control Tower landing zone using an AWS CloudFormation template and service control policies (SCPs). You can deploy the custom template and policies to individual accounts and organizational units (OUs) within your organization.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://docs.builder-toolkit.partner.aws.dev/docs-abp-project-type/docs/launch-using-cloudformation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.builder-toolkit.partner.aws.dev/docs-abp-project-type/docs/launch-using-cloudformation/</guid><description>Launch ABI using CloudFormation Templates Launch the cloudformation template provided as part /templates/ in the Management Account of the organization.
Download the cloudformation template from source: https://aws-abi-pilot.s3.us-east-1.amazonaws.com/cfn-abi-aws-reference-guide/templates/abi-enable-partner1-securityhub-integration.yaml
Launch CloudFormation template in your AWS Control Tower home region.
Stack name: launch-abi-sample-partner-integration ARN of partner integration to turn on in AWS Security Hub: arn:aws:securityhub:$[taskcat_current_region]::product/cloud-custodian/cloud-custodian Leave the remaining values default. Choose both the Capabilities and select Submit to launch the stack.
[] I acknowledge that AWS CloudFormation might create IAM resources with custom names.</description></item></channel></rss>